

Junior web developer with a passion for front-end & UI/UX design

Personal Profile

Coming from a creative background into the tech industry has been a rewarding and exciting experience. I have learnt a great deal about web development, but it's also allowed me to develop my communicational, organisational and problem solving skills.

During the School Of Code bootcamp, I enjoyed working with all of the various "stacks", but I particularly enjoyed working on the UI/UX designs and front-end development.

Interests

When I'm not coding, I enjoy learning French on Duolingo, where I have an 800+ day streak. I also like to photograph stars and landscapes. To stay healthy I enjoy cooking, cycling and yoga. On weekends, I like to play with my swing band at dance events throughout the country.



https://github.com/jimlikesjazz



https://www.linkedin.com/in/jimwynn-29281b67/

Experience

Full-Stack Developer

School Of Code // April 2022 - Aug 2022

- 16-week intensive bootcamp using a range of technologies to solve real-world problems.
- Working in 13 diverse teams; mainly pair programming but also larger teams for a weeklong project and a four-week final project at the end of the bootcamp.
- Front-end and back-end experience as well as UI/UX design.

Final Project (https://your-local-foodbank.netlify.app/):

- In a team of six, created a full-stack application to help foodbanks to better communicate with their communities.
- Application was built using React, CSS, MongoDB, Formik & Auth0.
- All team members rotated between front-end and back-end to ensure understanding of the whole app, but I spent the most time on the front-end styling and user experience.
- Used agile methodologies including allocating a daily scrum master, daily stand-ups and retrospectives.
- Used a variety of project management & design tools including: Trello, Slack, Miro & Figma.

Skills

- Languages: HTML5, CSS, JavaScript, SQL
- Design: Miro, Figma, Photoshop & Affinity Photo
- Libraries & Frameworks: React, Express.js
- Databases: PostgreSQL, MongoDB

Other Experience

Music Teacher, Jazz Pianist & Composer

2007 - Present

Education

BMus Jazz (hons), Birmingham Conservatoire

Degree classification: 2:1 // 2003 - 2007

A-Levels, New College Telford

Computing, ICT & Music // 2000 - 2002